[
    {
        "question": "1. (401) What valuable tool in the electric shop will show you the physical location of distribution system components?",
        "options": [
            "a. Schematic Drawing.",
            "b. One Line Diagram.",
            "c. As-Built Drawing.",
            "d. Distribution Map."
        ],
        "correct": "d. Distribution Map."
    },
    {
        "question": "2. (401) What informs electric shop personnel of unique conditions on the distribution system?",
        "options": [
            "a. Switching Chart.",
            "b. Distribution Map.",
            "c. One Line Diagram.",
            "d. Abnormal Conditions listing."
        ],
        "correct": "d. Abnormal Conditions listing."
    },
    {
        "question": "3. (402) What types of conductor support construction should be used on distribution systems locatedin high moisture environments?",
        "options": [
            "a. Steel Crossarms or Fiberglass Crossarms.",
            "b. Fiberglass Crossarms or Wood Crossarms.",
            "c. Epoxy Fiberglass Arms or Steel Crossarms.",
            "d. Fiberglass Crossarms or Epoxy Fiberglass Arms."
        ],
        "correct": "d. Fiberglass Crossarms or Epoxy Fiberglass Arms."
    },
    {
        "question": "4. (402) What insulator type is commonly connected to one another?",
        "options": [
            "a. Pin.",
            "b. Strain.",
            "c. Deadend.",
            "d. Suspension."
        ],
        "correct": "d. Suspension."
    },
    {
        "question": "5. (402) What insulator will you use on low-voltage or neutral conductors?",
        "options": [
            "a. Pin.",
            "b. Strain.",
            "c. Spool.",
            "d. Suspension."
        ],
        "correct": "c. Spool."
    },
    {
        "question": "6. (402) What insulator is used to insulate guy wires?",
        "options": [
            "a. Pin.",
            "b. Strain.",
            "c. Spool.",
            "d. Suspension."
        ],
        "correct": "b. Strain."
    },
    {
        "question": "7. (402) The American National Standards Institute class of an insulator is determined by the",
        "options": [
            "a. operating voltage.",
            "b. atmospheric pollution.",
            "c. atmospheric pollution and arcing voltage.",
            "d. atmospheric pollution and operating voltage."
        ],
        "correct": "d. atmospheric pollution and operating voltage."
    },
    {
        "question": "8. (403) In addition to engineers or the planning section, who assists in making a \"staking sheet\" of the area over which the line is to pass?",
        "options": [
            "a. A line crew.",
            "b. A survey crew.",
            "c. The graphics shop.",
            "d. The electrical supervisor."
        ],
        "correct": "b. A survey crew."
    },
    {
        "question": "9. (403) The AF Form 103, Base Civil Engineering Work Clearance Request, is used for",
        "options": [
            "a. staking sheets.",
            "b. digging permits.",
            "c. right-of-way requests.",
            "d. overhead line locations."
        ],
        "correct": "b. digging permits."
    },
    {
        "question": "10. (404) How many inches deeper do we set poles that are subject to more strain than normal?",
        "options": [
            "a. 2.",
            "b. 4.",
            "c. 6.",
            "d. 8."
        ],
        "correct": "c. 6."
    },
    {
        "question": "11. (405) What tool do workers use to position poles on the ground?",
        "options": [
            "a. Pike pole.",
            "b. Cant hook.",
            "c. Digging bar.",
            "d. Tamping bar."
        ],
        "correct": "b. Cant hook."
    },
    {
        "question": "12. (405) A large number of poles to be stored are sorted by",
        "options": [
            "a. class.",
            "b. length.",
            "c. length and class.",
            "d. length and type of treatment."
        ],
        "correct": "b. length."
    },
    {
        "question": "13. (405) We usually load poles on a trailer using the",
        "options": [
            "a. boom method.",
            "b. A-frame method.",
            "c. gin-pole method.",
            "d. snatch-block method."
        ],
        "correct": "a. boom method."
    },
    {
        "question": "14. (406) Where is a wood pole \"branded\"?",
        "options": [
            "a. At the top.",
            "b. On the bottom.",
            "c. 5 feet from the top.",
            "d. 10 feet up from the butt."
        ],
        "correct": "d. 10 feet up from the butt."
    },
    {
        "question": "15. (406) Where local conditions shorten the life of wood poles which pole is preferred?",
        "options": [
            "a. Steel.",
            "b. Concrete.",
            "c. Aluminum.",
            "d. Fiberglass."
        ],
        "correct": "b. Concrete."
    },
    {
        "question": "16. (406) Aluminum poles are most likely used for",
        "options": [
            "a. distribution lines.",
            "b. transmission lines.",
            "c. secondary service drops.",
            "d. roadway and area lighting circuits."
        ],
        "correct": "d. roadway and area lighting circuits."
    },
    {
        "question": "17. (407) What type of roof do we find on untreated wood poles?",
        "options": [
            "a. Slant.",
            "b. Gable.",
            "c. Conical.",
            "d. Double-cut.."
        ],
        "correct": "a. Slant."
    },
    {
        "question": "18. (407) What must you do before you cut the roof on a wood pole?",
        "options": [
            "a. Locate the front of pole.",
            "b. Chock both sides of pole.",
            "c. Locate balance point of pole.",
            "d. Find the pole's face side and back side."
        ],
        "correct": "d. Find the pole's face side and back side."
    },
    {
        "question": "19. (407) What size wood bit do you use to drill the hole for a crossarm through-bolt?",
        "options": [
            "a. 7/16-inch.",
            "b. 9/16-inch.",
            "c. 11/16-inch.",
            "d. 13/16-inch."
        ],
        "correct": "c. 11/16-inch."
    },
    {
        "question": "20. (408) In using the line truck and winch to set a pole, before you raise the pole slightly attach the winch line",
        "options": [
            "a. above the midpoint of the pole.",
            "b. above the butt end of the pole.",
            "c. below the top of the pole.",
            "d. below the crossarm."
        ],
        "correct": "a. above the midpoint of the pole."
    },
    {
        "question": "21. (408) If a pole must be set in an energized line, what two additional articles of equipment must be used?",
        "options": [
            "a. Wire tong and pulling rope.",
            "b. Rubber gloves and pole guard.",
            "c. Pole guard and conductor spreader.",
            "d. Pulling rope and conductor spreader."
        ],
        "correct": "b. Rubber gloves and pole guard."
    },
    {
        "question": "22. (409) The proper type of pole anchor depends largely upon",
        "options": [
            "a. pole height.",
            "b. soil conditions.",
            "c. length of conductor span.",
            "d. wind and snow conditions."
        ],
        "correct": "b. soil conditions."
    },
    {
        "question": "23. (409) What type of anchor do we use for hard or compact soil?",
        "options": [
            "a. Cone.",
            "b. Screw.",
            "c. Expanding.",
            "d. Log deadman."
        ],
        "correct": "c. Expanding."
    },
    {
        "question": "24. (409) What type of guy do we normally use at a curve in the line?",
        "options": [
            "a. Side guy.",
            "b. Span guy.",
            "c. Down guy.",
            "d. Corner guy."
        ],
        "correct": "a. Side guy."
    },
    {
        "question": "25. (409) Which of these combinations do you use to draw up a guy wire and hold it in place for attachment to the anchor rod?",
        "options": [
            "a. Crimps and winch line.",
            "b. Chain hoist and two strand grips.",
            "c. Sheave attachment and cable puller.",
            "d. Cable attachment and two thimble-eyes."
        ],
        "correct": "b. Chain hoist and two strand grips."
    },
    {
        "question": "26. (410) What factors are considered when establishing the three loading areas for conductors in theUnited States?",
        "options": [
            "a. Latitudinal and transversal loading.",
            "b. Longitudinal and horizontal loading.",
            "c. Horizontal, longitudinal, and vertical loading.",
            "d. Longitudinal, transverse, and vertical loading."
        ],
        "correct": "d. Longitudinal, transverse, and vertical loading."
    },
    {
        "question": "27. (411) How far apart are the pole pins spaced for a 12.470 kilovolt line?",
        "options": [
            "a. 18 inches.",
            "b. 24 inches.",
            "c. 30 inches.",
            "d. 36 inches."
        ],
        "correct": "c. 30 inches."
    },
    {
        "question": "28. (411) In vertical construction, where do we install the first conductor in relation to the top of the utility pole?",
        "options": [
            "a. 9 inches below the top.",
            "b. 12 inches below the top.",
            "c. 18 inches below the top.",
            "d. 24 inches below the top."
        ],
        "correct": "a. 9 inches below the top."
    },
    {
        "question": "29. (411) When raising a crossarm the person on the ground uses",
        "options": [
            "a. two clove hitches.",
            "b. a bowline and half hitch.",
            "c. a half hitch and clove hitch.",
            "d. a lineman's hitch and bowline."
        ],
        "correct": "c. a half hitch and clove hitch."
    },
    {
        "question": "30. (412) You use a conductor pulled from pole to pole over the crossarms instead of first laying it out on the ground when",
        "options": [
            "a. the area is very wet.",
            "b. very small wire is used.",
            "c. the ground is rough or stony.",
            "d. there are many trees in the area."
        ],
        "correct": "c. the ground is rough or stony."
    },
    {
        "question": "31. (412) When building a new pole line, if you are on the second pole which conductor does the person on the ground send up first?",
        "options": [
            "a. \"A\" phase.",
            "b. The neutral.",
            "c. The inside conductor.",
            "d. The outside conductor."
        ],
        "correct": "c. The inside conductor."
    },
    {
        "question": "32. (413) Which splice uses tapered jaws to hold the conductor?",
        "options": [
            "a. Compression.",
            "b. Twist sleeve.",
            "c. Sleeve joint.",
            "d. Automatic."
        ],
        "correct": "d. Automatic."
    },
    {
        "question": "33. (413) What do you do to prevent a hot-line clamp from burning a main conductor?",
        "options": [
            "a. Use a stirrup.",
            "b. Use only similar metals.",
            "c. Ensure hot-line clamps are put on tight.",
            "d. Attach hot-line clamps onto armor rods and tie wires."
        ],
        "correct": "a. Use a stirrup."
    },
    {
        "question": "34. (414) What type of insulator is used at the dead end for a primary conductor?",
        "options": [
            "a. Pin.",
            "b. Post.",
            "c. Strain.",
            "d. Suspension."
        ],
        "correct": "d. Suspension."
    },
    {
        "question": "35. (414) How long after the preliminary sagging must you wait to allow conductors to \"creep\"?",
        "options": [
            "a. 30 minutes to 4 hours.",
            "b. 15 to 30 minutes.",
            "c. 4 to 6 hours.",
            "d. 6 to 8 hours.‚õïý"
        ],
        "correct": "a. 30 minutes to 4 hours."
    },
    {
        "question": "36. (414) What size tie wire do we use for No. 2 conductor?",
        "options": [
            "a. No. 8.",
            "b. No. 6.",
            "c. No. 4.",
            "d. No. 2."
        ],
        "correct": "c. No. 4."
    },
    {
        "question": "37. (415) Pad mounting is the preferred mounting method for what transformer size?",
        "options": [
            "a. 75 kilovolt-ampere (kVA).",
            "b. 100 kVA.",
            "c. 175 kVA.",
            "d. 225 kVA."
        ],
        "correct": "a. 75 kilovolt-ampere (kVA)."
    },
    {
        "question": "38. (415) Which method do we most likely use to install light, single-phase transformers?",
        "options": [
            "a. Gin-pole.",
            "b. Hand-line.",
            "c. Chain hoist.",
            "d. Block and tackle."
        ],
        "correct": "d. Block and tackle."
    },
    {
        "question": "39. (415) Where do you connect the top and bottom connection points of a transformer's lightning arrester?",
        "options": [
            "a. Top to transformer, bottom to fused cutout.",
            "b. Top to ground wire, bottom to transformer.",
            "c. Top to primary wire, bottom to fused cutout.",
            "d. Top to primary wire, bottom to ground wire."
        ],
        "correct": "d. Top to primary wire, bottom to ground wire."
    },
    {
        "question": "40. (416) What can we install to raise the power factor in a distribution circuit?",
        "options": [
            "a. Capacitors.",
            "b. Transformers.",
            "c. Sectionalizers.",
            "d. Variable resistors."
        ],
        "correct": "a. Capacitors."
    },
    {
        "question": "41. (416) What device do we use across a capacitor's terminals to gradually discharge the capacitor?",
        "options": [
            "a. Resistor.",
            "b. Condenser.",
            "c. Transformer.",
            "d. Shorting stick."
        ],
        "correct": "a. Resistor."
    },
    {
        "question": "42. (417) What minimum depth below grade should you install a 12,470 volts alternating current(VAC) circuit using rigid, nonmetallic conduit?",
        "options": [
            "a. 24 inches.",
            "b. 36 inches.",
            "c. 18 inches.",
            "d. 42 inches."
        ],
        "correct": "c. 18 inches."
    },
    {
        "question": "43. (417) Ducts that terminate in a building must be sealed to prevent",
        "options": [
            "a. fire and smoke from entering a building.",
            "b. insects and gases from entering a building.",
            "c. gases and rodents from entering a building.",
            "d. insects and rodents from entering a building."
        ],
        "correct": "c. gases and rodents from entering a building."
    },
    {
        "question": "44. (418) What information is marked on manhole covers?",
        "options": [
            "a. Cable direction.",
            "b. Circuit identification.",
            "c. Presence of high voltage.",
            "d. Ownership or type of utility."
        ],
        "correct": "d. Ownership or type of utility."
    },
    {
        "question": "45. (418) What is the minimum size of a constructed manhole?",
        "options": [
            "a. 4 feet by 6 feet by 6 feet.",
            "b. 6 feet by 7 feet by 6 feet.",
            "c. 8 feet by 8 feet by 8 feet.",
            "d. 8 feet by 10 feet by 8 feet."
        ],
        "correct": "a. 4 feet by 6 feet by 6 feet."
    },
    {
        "question": "46. (418) The use of 90° bends in duct lines is permitted for",
        "options": [
            "a. pole risers.",
            "b. stranded copper cables.",
            "c. duct runs of less than 50 feet.",
            "d. cables that are no. 2 AWG or smaller."
        ],
        "correct": "a. pole risers."
    },
    {
        "question": "47. (419) What is the purpose of a vault?",
        "options": [
            "a. House multiple cable racks.",
            "b. Isolate electrical equipment.",
            "c. House submersible regulators.",
            "d. Open faulted underground cable."
        ],
        "correct": "b. Isolate electrical equipment."
    },
    {
        "question": "48. (419) Junction boxes located in an underground vault must",
        "options": [
            "a. be painted.",
            "b. have ventilation ports.",
            "c. provide a water-tight seal.",
            "d. be no smaller than 24 inches."
        ],
        "correct": "c. provide a water-tight seal."
    },
    {
        "question": "49. (420) The mechanical strength of underground cable is not a major concern because the cable is",
        "options": [
            "a. insulated.",
            "b. hard drawn.",
            "c. not under tension.",
            "d. kept cooler underground."
        ],
        "correct": "c. not under tension."
    },
    {
        "question": "50. (420) What material is used between the conductor and the cable insulation?",
        "options": [
            "a. Metal braid.",
            "b. Plastic sheath.",
            "c. Varnish cambric.",
            "d. Strand shielding."
        ],
        "correct": "d. Strand shielding."
    },
    {
        "question": "51. (421) When pulling cable, the snatch block and pulling rope is attached to",
        "options": [
            "a. a wire rope and flexible duct.",
            "b. coupling rods in the manhole.",
            "c. the pulling-in iron in the manhole.",
            "d. a wire rope and flexible steel conduit."
        ],
        "correct": "c. the pulling-in iron in the manhole."
    },
    {
        "question": "52. (421) What is the device used to attach the underground cable to the pulling rope?",
        "options": [
            "a. Snatch block.",
            "b. Feeding tube.",
            "c. Basket grip.",
            "d. Mandrel."
        ],
        "correct": "c. Basket grip."
    },
    {
        "question": "53. (422) Which procedure do you use to assure that a duct is clear of obstructions?",
        "options": [
            "a. Rigging.",
            "b. Drawing.",
            "c. Rodding.",
            "d. Swabbing."
        ],
        "correct": "c. Rodding."
    },
    {
        "question": "54. (422) Why is proper cable reel placement important?",
        "options": [
            "a. Ensures bend in the cable is not reversed.",
            "b. To allow the reel to be lubricated properly.",
            "c. Ensures cable is installed in the correct duct.",
            "d. Proper cable reel placement is not important."
        ],
        "correct": "a. Ensures bend in the cable is not reversed."
    },
    {
        "question": "55. (422) How many people does it take to pull underground cable safely using the winch method?",
        "options": [
            "a. 4.",
            "b. 5.",
            "c. 6.",
            "d. 7."
        ],
        "correct": "b. 5."
    },
    {
        "question": "56. (423) What term describes an underground cable that is brought up through a conduit and attached to an overhead line?",
        "options": [
            "a. Riser.",
            "b. Duct run.",
            "c. Termination.",
            "d. Transition duct."
        ],
        "correct": "a. Riser."
    },
    {
        "question": "57. (423) The device used to terminate high-voltage cables is called a",
        "options": [
            "a. high-voltage termination.",
            "b. skirted cable end seal.",
            "c. skirted weatherhead.",
            "d. conduit riser."
        ],
        "correct": "a. high-voltage termination."
    },
    {
        "question": "58. (424) When making a load-break elbow, before attaching the crimp connector to the cable make sure you",
        "options": [
            "a. clean the cable with alcohol.",
            "b. apply corrosion inhibitor to the cable.",
            "c. align the hole on the end of the connector with the equipment bushing.",
            "d. apply semi-conducting tape to the conductor for the length of the elbow."
        ],
        "correct": "c. align the hole on the end of the connector with the equipment bushing."
    },
    {
        "question": "59. (424) After sliding the elbow over the connector and cable the next step is to",
        "options": [
            "a. attach the threaded electrode to the connector using a pair of adjustable pliers.",
            "b. thread the electrode into the connector using the wrench from the elbow kit.",
            "c. thread the electrode into the connector until it is hand tight.",
            "d. crimp the electrode onto the connector."
        ],
        "correct": "b. thread the electrode into the connector using the wrench from the elbow kit."
    },
    {
        "question": "60. (425) What depth do you dig the trench for a below-ground check of a pole?",
        "options": [
            "a. 4 to 6 inches.",
            "b. 8 to 18 inches.",
            "c. 12 to 24 inches.",
            "d. 24 to 36 inches."
        ],
        "correct": "b. 8 to 18 inches."
    },
    {
        "question": "61. (425) Decay usually starts at what location on a crossarm?",
        "options": [
            "a. Top.",
            "b. Ends.",
            "c. Bottom.",
            "d. Pin holes."
        ],
        "correct": "d. Pin holes."
    },
    {
        "question": "62. (425) What condition can cause a crossarm to twist?",
        "options": [
            "a. Improper sag.",
            "b. Lightning or voltage surges.",
            "c. Unbalanced strain or insufficient guying.",
            "d. Crossarm unseasoned when it was installed."
        ],
        "correct": "c. Unbalanced strain or insufficient guying."
    },
    {
        "question": "63. (426) When a span shows too much sag while adjacent spans appear normal,",
        "options": [
            "a. the conductor has stretched from being hit by a falling object.",
            "b. the cause is a twisted crossarm.",
            "c. it's a sign of loose tie wires.",
            "d. it's a result of poor guying."
        ],
        "correct": "a. the conductor has stretched from being hit by a falling object."
    },
    {
        "question": "64. (426) We must make voltage and current readings on capacitor installations at least",
        "options": [
            "a. annually.",
            "b. twice a year.",
            "c. 4 times a year.",
            "d. 6 times a year."
        ],
        "correct": "c. 4 times a year."
    },
    {
        "question": "65. (427) What do we use to cut tree limbs that are beyond arm's reach?",
        "options": [
            "a. Pole saw.",
            "b. Forester saw.",
            "c. Docking saw.",
            "d. Crosscut saw."
        ],
        "correct": "a. Pole saw."
    },
    {
        "question": "66. (427) Where would you put the tree pruner to add a third section?",
        "options": [
            "a. Send it to the shop.",
            "b. Lay it flat on the ground.",
            "c. Lean it against a tree limb.",
            "d. Lay it across the truck bed."
        ],
        "correct": "c. Lean it against a tree limb."
    },
    {
        "question": "67. (427) What species of trees do we usually top?",
        "options": [
            "a. Spruce, pine, and fir.",
            "b. Pine, elm, and pecan.",
            "c. Oak, elm, and hackberry.",
            "d. Willow, cottonwood, and poplar."
        ],
        "correct": "d. Willow, cottonwood, and poplar."
    },
    {
        "question": "68. (428) What is usually the first step in troubleshooting a tripped overhead distribution circuit?",
        "options": [
            "a. Test the circuit.",
            "b. Inspect the circuit visually.",
            "c. Apply necessary ground sets.",
            "d. Try to reset the circuit's recloser."
        ],
        "correct": "b. Inspect the circuit visually."
    },
    {
        "question": "69. (428) What do we use to test a distribution line for a ground?",
        "options": [
            "a. Megger.",
            "b. Ammeter.",
            "c. Voltmeter.",
            "d. Phase rotation meter."
        ],
        "correct": "a. Megger."
    },
    {
        "question": "70. (428) Which of these is not one of the three main causes of power line noise?",
        "options": [
            "a. Defective equipment insulation.",
            "b. Bonded ground wires on the utility pole.",
            "c. Electrostatic leakage from ungrounded hardware.",
            "d. Loose connections in the primary or neutral circuit."
        ],
        "correct": "b. Bonded ground wires on the utility pole."
    },
    {
        "question": "71. (429) What must the electrician do before working on deenergized lines?",
        "options": [
            "a. Notify reporting official.",
            "b. Test and ground the lines.",
            "c. Close the normally open switch.",
            "d. Don rubber protective equipment."
        ],
        "correct": "b. Test and ground the lines."
    },
    {
        "question": "72. (429) How is the cable used for ground sets constructed?",
        "options": [
            "a. 600-volts insulated rubber or synthetic-covered flexible copper.",
            "b. 5,000-volts insulated rubber or synthetic-covered flexible copper.",
            "c. 600-volts insulated rubber or synthetic-covered hard-drawn copper.",
            "d. 5,000-volts insulated rubber or synthetic-covered hard-drawn copper."
        ],
        "correct": "a. 600-volts insulated rubber or synthetic-covered flexible copper."
    },
    {
        "question": "73. (430) When a break occurs in an energized line, how is the line at the break affected?",
        "options": [
            "a. Both ends of the wire are melted.",
            "b. Both ends of the wire are hardened.",
            "c. The whole wire get very brittle and charred.",
            "d. The center disappears, leaving soft wire on either side."
        ],
        "correct": "d. The center disappears, leaving soft wire on either side."
    },
    {
        "question": "74. (430) What do you use to check a suspected damaged transformer?",
        "options": [
            "a. Megger.",
            "b. Oil tester.",
            "c. Voltmeter.",
            "d. Clamp-on ammeter."
        ],
        "correct": "a. Megger."
    },
    {
        "question": "75. (431) What must you do before working on energized lines?",
        "options": [
            "a. Inspect the utility pole for heart-rot.",
            "b. Fill out AF Form 980, Caution Abnormal Conditions tag.",
            "c. Inspect hot line tools and equipment for proper operation.",
            "d. Fill out AF Form 103, Base Civil Engineering Work Clearance Request."
        ],
        "correct": "c. Inspect hot line tools and equipment for proper operation."
    },
    {
        "question": "76. (431) What two connector types do we use when splicing energized conductors?",
        "options": [
            "a. Split-bolt and automatic.",
            "b. Compression and automatic.",
            "c. Hot line clamp and split-bolt.",
            "d. Compression and hot line clamp."
        ],
        "correct": "b. Compression and automatic."
    },
    {
        "question": "77. (431) In making a midspan splice on an energized line, position the personnel bucket of the bucket truck",
        "options": [
            "a. at a 45° angle to the break.",
            "b. parallel to the area to be spliced.",
            "c. directly under the area to be spliced.",
            "d. so the linemen can face the splice area from the front of the bucket."
        ],
        "correct": "d. so the linemen can face the splice area from the front of the bucket."
    },
    {
        "question": "78. (432) What tie stick head do we normally use to untie tie wires?",
        "options": [
            "a. Fixed head.",
            "b. Rotary blade.",
            "c. Rotary prong.",
            "d. Double prong."
        ],
        "correct": "b. Rotary blade."
    },
    {
        "question": "79. (432) Once we untie the tie wires what do we use to raise the auxiliary crossarm assembly?",
        "options": [
            "a. Wire tongs.",
            "b. A handline.",
            "c. The mast pole.",
            "d. A snatch block."
        ],
        "correct": "d. A snatch block."
    },
    {
        "question": "80. (433) When the pole has a single crossarm supporting three phase conductors how many line hoses are needed for a pole change?",
        "options": [
            "a. 8.",
            "b. 10.",
            "c. 12.",
            "d. 14."
        ],
        "correct": "a. 8."
    },
    {
        "question": "81. (433) When replacing a pole, how many feet above the pole do you raise the auxiliary arm?",
        "options": [
            "a. 3 to 4 feet.",
            "b. 5 to 6 feet.",
            "c. 6 to 7 feet.",
            "d. 7 to 8 feet."
        ],
        "correct": "a. 3 to 4 feet."
    },
    {
        "question": "82. (433) The high voltage audible indicator makes an audible sound when placed",
        "options": [
            "a. on a hot stick.",
            "b. on the utility pole.",
            "c. in the bucket truck.",
            "d. in an electrostatic field."
        ],
        "correct": "d. in an electrostatic field."
    },
    {
        "question": "83. (434) The act of tying a tagline to each outside conductor with a bowline knot and pulling the conductors out of the work area is called",
        "options": [
            "conductors out of the work area is called",
            "a. tying off.",
            "b. bowlining.",
            "c. tagging out.",
            "d. line knotting."
        ],
        "correct": "c. tagging out."
    },
    {
        "question": "84. (434) After you remove the crossarm, who lowers it to the ground?",
        "options": [
            "a. The linemen.",
            "b. The supervisor.",
            "c. The ground person.",
            "d. The ranking 5-level."
        ],
        "correct": "c. The ground person."
    },
    {
        "question": "85. (435) Service meters are used to determine",
        "options": [
            "a. if sufficient voltage is reaching a facility or organization.",
            "b. how large a service is needed for a facility or organization.",
            "c. if sufficient amperage is reaching a facility or organization.",
            "d. how much power has been used by a facility or organization."
        ],
        "correct": "d. how much power has been used by a facility or organization."
    },
    {
        "question": "86. (435) The service meter normally measures",
        "options": [
            "a. kilowatts.",
            "b. volt-amps.",
            "c. power factor.",
            "d. kilowatt-hours."
        ],
        "correct": "d. kilowatt-hours."
    },
    {
        "question": "87. (435) What is the formula to find the amount of watt-hours used?",
        "options": [
            "a. Volts multiplied by amps.",
            "b. Power factor times wattage.",
            "c. Multiplier times the previous reading.",
            "d. New reading minus the previous reading."
        ],
        "correct": "d. New reading minus the previous reading."
    },
    {
        "question": "88. (435) When transposing the numbers from the dial meter to a piece of paper, start on the.",
        "options": [
            "a. right hand dial then work to the left.",
            "b. left hand dial then work to the right.",
            "c. top dial then work to the bottom.",
            "d. bottom dial then work to the top."
        ],
        "correct": "a. right hand dial then work to the left."
    },
    {
        "question": "89. (436) What is the approximate bending radius for underground cable?",
        "options": [
            "a. 5 to 12 times cable diameter.",
            "b. 10 to 15 times cable diameter.",
            "c. 5 to 12 times insulation thickness.",
            "d. 10 to 15 times insulation thickness."
        ],
        "correct": "a. 5 to 12 times cable diameter."
    },
    {
        "question": "90. (436) How much straight cable needs to exist on each side of a cable splice for racking purposes?",
        "options": [
            "a. 6 inches.",
            "b. 12 inches.",
            "c. 1 ½ feet.",
            "d. 2 feet."
        ],
        "correct": "a. 6 inches."
    },
    {
        "question": "91. (436) What type of tape is used for fireproofing underground cable in manholes?",
        "options": [
            "a. Asbestos.",
            "b. Waxed nylon.",
            "c. Aluminum shielding.",
            "d. Polymeric elastomer."
        ],
        "correct": "d. Polymeric elastomer."
    },
    {
        "question": "92. (436) What type of cable test is made after its installed but before it is placed into service?",
        "options": [
            "a. Proof test.",
            "b. Factory test.",
            "c. Acceptance test.",
            "d. Maintenance test."
        ],
        "correct": "c. Acceptance test."
    },
    {
        "question": "93. (436) Generally if a cable's insulation is deteriorating, what does a direct current high potential(DC Hypot) cable test indicate for each succeeding test?",
        "options": [
            "a. Lower resistance or a lower power factor.",
            "b. Lower resistance or a higher power factor.",
            "c. Higher resistance or a lower power factor.",
            "d. Higher resistance or a higher power factor."
        ],
        "correct": "b. Lower resistance or a higher power factor."
    },
    {
        "question": "94. (437) What is the easiest and quickest way to locate a cable fault?",
        "options": [
            "a. Visually.",
            "b. Ohm method.",
            "c. Tracer method.",
            "d. Re-energizing the circuit."
        ],
        "correct": "a. Visually."
    },
    {
        "question": "95. (437) When you check for a grounded conductor with a volt-ohmmeter, what reading would indicate a grounded conductor?",
        "options": [
            "a. Low voltage.",
            "b. High voltage.",
            "c. Low resistance.",
            "d. High resistance."
        ],
        "correct": "c. Low resistance."
    },
    {
        "question": "96. (437) When you use the mm-1 fault locator or the thumper to locate a cable fault, when you are over the fault location",
        "options": [
            "a. the signal increases with both testers.",
            "b. the signal decreases with both testers.",
            "c. fault locator signal increases at the fault; thumper signal decreases.",
            "d. fault locator signal fades out at the fault; thumper signal increases to the loudest volume."
        ],
        "correct":  "d. fault locator signal fades out at the fault; thumper signal increases to the loudest volume."
    },
    {
        "question": "97. (438) In many cases, a cable fault is located at a",
        "options": [
            "a. splice.",
            "b. duct entrance.",
            "c. bend in the cable.",
            "d. cable ground connection."
        ],
        "correct": "a. splice."
    },
    {
        "question": "98. (438) Which cable splice kit requires the most labor to install?",
        "options": [
            "a. Heat-shrinkable.",
            "b. Power cable joint.",
            "c. Conventional taped splice kit.",
            "d. Separable insulated connectors."
        ],
        "correct": "c. Conventional taped splice kit."
    },
    {
        "question": "99. (439) What should be your first step when troubleshooting a pad mount transformer?",
        "options": [
            "a. Take a complete set of secondary phase-to-phase and phase-to-ground voltage readings.",
            "b. Take a complete set of primary phase-to-phase and phase-to-ground voltage readings.",
            "c. Take phase-to-phase voltage readings on the secondary side of the transformer.",
            "d. Take phase-to-ground voltage readings on the primary side."
        ],
        "correct": "a. Take a complete set of secondary phase-to-phase and phase-to-ground voltage readings."
    },
    {
        "question": "100. (439) If tests indicate an off-ratio winding, how would you verify whether or not the problem was in the transformer?",
        "options": [
            "a. Take primary current readings on all three phases.",
            "b. Take secondary current readings on all three phases.",
            "c. Take voltage readings on the primary side of the transformer.",
            "d. De-energize the transformer and take resistance readings on the transformer windings."
        ],
        "correct": "c. Take voltage readings on the primary side of the transformer."
    }
]